

Dean Rodel Legada

Full Stack Web Developer

About Me

Dedicated, detail-oriented, and certified Frontend Developer, Backend Developer, and Full Stack Web Developer with experience in developing ecommerce website using MERN tech stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js). I also engaged in several tools, languages, and frameworks such as: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Git bash, GitHub, Tailwind CSS, Angular, Typescript, Gitlab, Heroku, Postman, and Sublime Text and many more.

Lets talk about the task. *wink*

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | Webact Company 06/2022 - 05/2023

Key responsibilities:

- conceptualized project from scratch. Built reusable components following atomic design methodology.
- developed Widgets and new features based on customers requests
- Work with users to determine their needs and then design.
- Maintaining and making an updates into a Website using PHP Laravel.
- observed clean code and reusability
- collaborated with other team members in developing project features.

My Contact

deanzdeluxe@gmail.com

(+63-936-898-5409

• Esperanza, Sultan Kudarat, Philippines

https://deanrodellegadaportfolio.netlif y.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dean-rodel-legada-12b325197/

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~ 017d16da165b5423c2s=111058075510792

Digital Skills

Frontend Development

- ReactNextis
- Responsive
 Web Design
- HTML5/CSS, Javascript
- React Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Laravel
- TypeScript
- Tailwind CSS

Backend Development

• Express.JS

Rest API

• Node.js

Database Management

NoSQL (MongoDB)

DevOps

• Git (Version Control)

Data Miner/Marketer | USPTO - FREELANCER

04/2020 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Collecting Data such as emails and phone number from clients provided website
- maintaining an accurate data before sending it back to clients.

eCOMMERCE WEBSITE - MERN Tech Stack: MongoDB, React, Express, Node

https://fullstack-capstone3-capstone3-final-seven.vercel.app/

A full-stack E-commerce application made mainly with MERN stack technologies

- the app has 2 users: admin and regular user(customer)
- user can add item/s from cart provided user is already logged in otherwise the app will redirect user to login page when trying to add item to cart.
- admin can do CREATE and Retrieve for user/s and product and backend will check if user is authorize to
- do so
- · otherwise it will redirect to home page

My Portfolio - Frontend webpage using ReactJs

https://deanrodellegada-portfolio.netlify.app/

A Frontend portfolio webpage made mainly with ReactJs

- the webpage describe more information about me.
- showcasing my previous projects made using ReactJs and MERN Teck Stack
- also includes my contact information where clients can create a message.

Wedding Invitation - Frontend webpage using ReactJs

https://deanrodellegada-portfolio.netlify.app/static/media/cjwedding.be28063c62ef7763f7la.png

- · Wedding Invitation
- Information about the wedding and its location.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Frontend Developement - HTML,CSS,Javascript

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/e792e78c-c726-4bd2-aa9d-e90617d4a4f2 02/2022 - 03/2022 www.zuitt.co

BackEnd Development - Restful API, ExpressJs, NodeJs

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/8c2a407b-c535-496a-aadd-9ce8eaef729f 03/2022 - 04/2022 www.zuitt.co

Full Stack Development - MERN Tech Stack: MongoDB, React, Express, Node

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/4814fb2a-51f7-408d-b796-44082fcdfe35 04/2022 - 05/2022 www.zuitt.co

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN – freeCodeCamp

12/2021 - 02/2022

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION SYSTEM – STI-Colliege Koronadal

06/2018 - 07/2020 - Santa Lucia St, Poblacion, Koronadal, Philippines